Good afternoon Greetings from Ukraine
Добрый день Привет из Украины
I am from Austria, originally from this place,
Я из Австрии родом из это место
I immediately give different positions to people
я у людей сразу ихнюю позицию
if they are for Russia, then they are
разные дают если они за Россию тогда вот
spinning these events for 14 years,
раскручивают эти события 14 года как
so that they don’t say
чтобы не сказали
at 16, it
в 16
turns out at 14, they caught Yes, it’s all
получается в 14 застали Да это все
just
просто
Ukraine there killed this mine  and the
Украина там убивал это минных и
then pancake Until
тогдашний блин Пока не начались военные
hostilities began until the Russians came, these
действия пока не пришли русские эти
were no rallies at all, there were
вообще не было митинга были
Russians to understand in Ukraine, there may be a
русских понять в Украине могут быть
rally of long rallies, this is already something
митинг длинных митинг это уже что-то
terrible, that is, this is impossible
страшное то есть такое невозможно
, a
возможно
political process is possible For us, this is the norm
политический процесс Для нас это норма
for them, like everything if a rally  this is already
для них типа все если митинг это уже
shorter than the type, almost the content
короче типа чуть ли не содержание
can be there Solitary people went out there
может быть там Одиночный люди вышли там
at the peak from solitary people living there with a poster
на пике от одиночные там плакатом
living in another world. We somehow went
живут в другом Еще мире мы пошли как-то
forward as well as possible in the past, and
вперед также как можно не в прошлом и
just like some Europeans, maybe they
также как некоторые европейцы может нас
didn’t understand us in something -  then So we, too, somewhere
не понимали в чем-то Так мы тоже где-то
else from everything soviet did not throw off
еще от всего совкового не сбросились так
and they look at us, too, as if I don’t understand
и смотрят на нас тоже как вот не понимаю
what we have. This is the Soviet Legacy and
что мы имеем Вот это совковое Наследие и
we are fighting. So we went  we are going somewhere we are moving
мы боремся Так мы идем куда-то двигаемся
towards reforms we are moving towards civilized
в реформы двигаемся к цивилизованным
countries so yes it is a sick path it is not
странам так да это больной путь это не
so easy Because if a person
так просто Потому что если человек
wants to change himself it is not done in
хочет себя изменить это не делается за
one day there is also a country and Russian
один день также есть страна а русский
Here they are not They closed Europe West
Вот они нет Они закрылись Европа Запад
This is bad but all the officials
Это плохо но все чиновники
their children don’t live studying abroad
учатся за границей дети их не живут
investigation
расследование
children all in Austria took pictures of cars E
дети все в Австрии машины фоткались Э
that they are catching up to the west but the children now
что они на запад нагоняют но дети сейчас
even live in their venihi and says so and
даже живут венихи ихние и так говорит и
here yes it doesn’t fit at all I
сюда да вообще не состыковывает мне тут
here recently with the Russians also talked to
один недавно с россиянам тоже общался
me says also there for the war  Yes, of
мне говорит тоже там за войну зашло и Да
course, everything is bad in Ukraine. This is
это конечно все плохо в Украине Вот это
horror, what is happening, this is the
ужас что происходит вот это вот
oppression of the Russian language, this is
притеснение русского языка это ужас
some kind of horror.
какой-то Прикинь скотина какая там людей
Haven’t been to Moscow even like this in
они не Бывали в Москве даже вот так в
theircountry,
своей стране
some values ​​Why Yes, but they don’t have
какие-то ценности Почему Так а у них не
it I often ask a question, for example,
так Я вот задаю вопрос часто например
people there Scott there Tatarstan Bash  kiriy
люди там Скотта там Татарстана Башкирии
there Why is a guy in the Czech Republic who has no
там Почему парень в Чехии у которой нету
resources who conditionally buy gas
ресурсов которые покупают условно газ
oil from Russia and even pay
нефть у России да еще платят России
money to Russia lives better than you here in a country with
деньги живет лучше чем ты тут в стране с
these resources And in short, such
этими ресурсами И короче такие
fantastic ones start
фантастические начинаются
further Here you in Ukraine also poorly
дальше Вот вас в Украине тоже плохо это
understand this If I, for example, am I  I was in Austria,
понимают Если я например я был в Австрии
I see the difference in the standard of living,
я вижу разницу в уровне жизни
infrastructure, the difference in people When
инфраструктуре разницу люди Когда
they come, they want
приезжают они хотят
social standards, they try to
стандарты социальные они стараются
raise up We have a lot of people there
подтягивать У нас очень много людей там
in Europe, they worked So they
в Европе работала Так ездит
go to work, go on excursions,
поехать на работу поехать на экскурсии
even so, people come to some cafes of
даже так люди приезжают какие-то кафешки
people I already have  it was shorter on the stream, the
людей уже у меня было на стриме короче
men from Pskov near the zone next to the
мужики с Пскова рядом зоне рядом с
European Union and they don’t brag that they have
евросоюзом и не вот хвастаются что у них
a key super repair plasma in their village, the
в деревне ключевой супер ремонт плазма
whole game will fall off the toilet on the street
все игру отвалит туалет на улице хочу
like there is a
морозить ушу оделся типа там
foam pad he bought himself a
пенопластовая накладка он себе купил
plasma
плазму
toilet
туалет не может этого парадигму дед срал
sad Yes And you know
и поэтому очень печально Да И вот знаешь
there is still such a topic of people in Donetsk
еще есть такая тема людей в Донецке
Luhansk in Russia they scare there that Europe
Луганские в России пугают там что Европа
is a gay parade
это гейпарады
they will not run and grab
они не будут бегать и короче хватать
your ass
тебя задницу
for some reason, everything is superfluous The elite in Europe
почему-то все лишнее Элита в Европе
lives in Europe and studies and it does not
живет в Европе учится и их это не
bother them Yes, what is there  there are about two gays there, by the
смущает Да что там их там где-то два гея
way,
кстати
nothing else a good standard of living a
больше ничего хороший уровень жизни
high level of education medicine
высокий уровень образования медицина
will be taken from the family
будет из семьи забирать
that they are not embarrassed by the fact that your Elite
что их не смущает то что твоя Элита
lives in fact back, she blows you here and
живет по сути назад она тут дует вас и
receives all the benefits in the west medicine I
все блага получает на западе медицина не
don’t think that they are
думаю что они
good good
хорошо хорошо
thank God
слава Богу
it’s nice to meet such a person
приятно до встретить такого человека
so to clap with Donetsk in the
так на мачты хлопать с Донецком в
sixteenth year I went there I went to
шестнадцатом году ехал туда поехал в
Austria will live there for days I don’t even want to
Австрию доживет там дней даже не хочет
return even after liberation a
возвращаться даже после освобождения
completely different mentality
совсем другое менталитет